Sukhasana, easy sitting pose.
We're going to learn to do Sukhasana with a belt, because oftentimes, as you're getting used to sitting on the floor, it's not that comfortable for your lower back.
But we can use a belt to support your lower back, and support the whole pose.
You're going to need at least a ten foot belt, and then you're just going to make it, hook the belt, and then make it equal.
You're going to take your belt behind your lower back.
Then as you've looped it, there's two loops.
You're going to put one on one knee; you're going to come around, and put it on the other knee.
Now I need to suggest that the buckle is not near your skin, because that's not going to be comfortable on you.
Once you have yourself locked in, you'll be able to lower the belt, and the belt is going to support the whole body, so that you can sit here and meditate if that's what you choose to do.
Then if this is not kind to your knees, which again, is a lot of things that happens when you're just getting started, find your blocks and rest the knees.
Create the length, receive and enjoy.